<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brands on InfluxData Branding Docs</title>
    <link>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brands on InfluxData Branding Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 16:11:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>InfluxData Brand Colors</title>
      <link>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 16:11:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/colors/</guid>
      <description>InfluxData Brand Colors    The Offical Brand Colors are intended for all use cases. It is effective for UI, marketing graphics, and everything in between.
Usage Rules  Do not use colors outside of these colors Never use true black #000000    Primary Colors   Deep Purple P0  #1F0A23  Pool P1  #22ADF6  White P2  #FFFFFF       Secondary Colors   Chartreuse S0  #D6F622  Magenta S1  #BF2FE5  Comet S2  #9394FF       Nuetrals There are many nuetrals because they are the most used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero Graphics</title>
      <link>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/hero-graphics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/hero-graphics/</guid>
      <description>Hero Graphics    Usage Rules  All Hero Graphics should incorporate each of these three elements: Data + Time + Action The following options for each element are available to use in your compositions    Data Data can be conceptual in the form of dimensional diagrams, or more literal representations of the various industries we serve and the types of data they generate
         Time A layer of time must be overlaid on top of our data layer; this can come in the form of timelines, stopwatch dials, radars, or equalizers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Messaging</title>
      <link>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/messaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/messaging/</guid>
      <description>Messaging       How We Speak   Values Voice Traits  Respect  Sincere  Humility  Plain-spoken  Action  Inspirational  Courage  Brave  Openness  Direct       What We Say   All Audiences Real time visibility into stacks, sensors, and systems The open-source time series database to instrument, observe, learn and automate any system, application and business process   Dev Audience Built for developers Easy to start, easy to scale Optimized for time to awesome, InfluxDB is purpose built for time series data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform</title>
      <link>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://influxdata.github.io/branding/brand/platform/</guid>
      <description>Brand Platform       Our Core Passion   Simplicity From the moment someone sets up InfluxDB, to the moment their time series data begins appearing, the magic of our product is that it is drop-dead simple. Everything we do and everything we say should reflect our commitment to making things as simple as possible.      Brand Platform   Vision  Data is best understoodthrough the lens of time Time series data is an emerging category, but the power our platform provides can help people understand any dataset in a new dimension.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>